geoguessr.com 2019-09-02

# GeoGuessr Privacy Policy

Adapted from [PrivacyChoice Privacy Policy.](http://www.privacychoice.org/resources)

### Data

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems or third parties also log information like your browser and operating system.

We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name and email address. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook and Twitter.

Our systems may associate this personal information with your activities in the course of providing service to you (such as pages you view or things you click on). We may also email you with special offers or upcoming information about our service. You can also, at any time, opt-out from receiving our marketing emails.

### GDPR and Protection rights

GeoGuessr would like to make sure you are fully aware of all your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:

**The right to access** – You have the right to request GeoGuessr for copies of your personal data.

**The right to recitification** – You have the right to request that GeoGuessr correct any information that you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request GeoGuessr to complete information you believe is Incomplete.

**The right to erasure** – You have the right to request that GeoGuessr erase your personal data, under certain conditions.

If you have any questions about the data we hold on you, please contact us. This information is based on guidance from the [GDPR.EU](https://gdpr.eu/) website.

### Location

To customize our service for you, we and our partners may collect, use, and share precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your computer or device. This location data is collected anonymously in a form that does not personally identify you and is used only to provide and improve our service.

### Access

You can sign into your account to see any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name and email.

### Sharing

We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name or email) with other companies.

### Security

We take reasonable administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to safeguard and protect your information from unauthorized access or disclosure. This includes utilizing Transport Layer Security (TLS) software, which encrypts the personal information you input. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business.

### Terms of Service

Please also read our Terms of Service
